cheapesttextbooks.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Statement - CheapestTextbooks.com

## Privacy Statement

Information Collection and Use  
When you send us an email asking us a question, we only use your email address for answering your question. We do not sell email addresses and we do not collect email addresses for any purpose.

Cookies  
CheapestTextbooks.com and some of our web advertising partners, use small strings of text (known as cookies) that are placed on your computer when you click on an ad. Cookies typically remain active on your computer for about 30 days. If you visit certain pages on our site during that period, CheapestTextbooks.com and some of our web advertising partners may be able to tell that you came to our site (but not user name, address, or other personal information) via an advertisment and/or left our site and went to one of our web advertising partner sites. 

If you want to disable the use of cookies, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some websites may not function properly if you refuse to accept cookies.

Third Party Advertising  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our Web advertising partners. Information about the users visit to this site, such as the number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.

Log Files  
Like most standard Web sites, we use log files. This includes (but is not limited to) internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Log files are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that CheapestTextbooks.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement so our users are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

Contact Information  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [ Contact Us](http://www.cheapesttextbooks.com/contact.html "Questions or Comments? Send us a message to let us know!") using our email submission format.

Sincerely,  
CheapestTextbooks.com  
a division of Intermarketings Inc.
